<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-12-14T15:06:19-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">notebook_0</title><subtitle>a place to put some writing</subtitle><entry><title type="html">fucked_up_0</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/13/fucked-up.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="fucked_up_0" /><published>2020-12-13T21:15:39-08:00</published><updated>2020-12-13T21:15:39-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/12/13/fucked-up</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/13/fucked-up.html">&lt;p&gt;She asks me if I want to see her naked. I guess in some ill-lit cave at the base of my brain stem, I do, but the human in me is tired and just wants to sleep. But I give a little smile and say Yes, because she is fragile in her offering, because she is timid and the forthrightness is difficult for her. If I told her No it would devastate her. She says Okay. She starts to fumble with the top button of her shirt – she is stiff with nerves, performing this part of a girl who knows what to do here. I laugh and put a hand on her hip and pull her toward where I am seated on the edge of the bed. I say Let me. She looks down at me and her hair falls into my eyes. She laughs now and arranges her hair over her shoulder. I reach for her top button and ask Can I? And she nods. I unbutton her shirt and she shrugs it off and looks at me as if for approval. I slide my hands over her thin shoulders and down to her waist and pretend to be more overcome with desire than I am. Normally I would not have to pretend, but at the moment I want to sleep. I put my head against her stomach and close my eyes. She runs her fingers through my hair and this does give me a rush of pleasure – I have always liked the feeling of someone’s nails tracing over my scalp. It gives me chills. I hook my fingers on the inside of her waistband and make my way around to the front and ask Can I, and she says Yes, and I unbutton her jeans and take them down without opening my eyes. I really am tired. I pull her down and onto my lap and hold onto her, and she holds my head but there is the lingering question of What now? I don’t know how to tell her I just want to sleep. After a minute she says We can just sleep, and I feel myself flush with gratitude. I laugh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read me, huh, I say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can read you, she says softly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry, I say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t be sorry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fall back into bed and pull her alongside me. She throws a leg over my legs and puts her head on my chest, a hand on the side of my neck. I close my eyes. She looks up at me every once in a while, maybe to check if I am still awake. I drift a bit into the semi-consciousness which is often the closest I can get to sleep with someone else in my bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you still think about her? she asks, so quietly that at first I think I am dreaming. I don’t open my eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, I say. Yeah. Is that okay?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you thinking about her now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what to say, I say. I feel her head move against my chest as she nods. She is quiet. I drift again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you wish she was here instead of me? she whispers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city quiets, pressed up in its dim blue light against the blinds. As if to listen in. A train passing under the distant highway overpass groans, and the cars race down Telegraph, their tires hissing on the pavement. Somewhere, an ambulance or fire truck wails and I think it is odd that I enjoy that sound, though it announces emergency, because from far off it reminds me of the city, becomes ambient, loses urgency. I am weightless in the event horizon of sleep. I hear that whisper over and over. It takes my breath away. By the time I realize I have not answered, her breathing is slow and deep and she twitches in the involuntary way of someone dreaming. I approach the asymptote of sleep, thinking of how fucked up I am over her, the other her, hearing that whisper over and over again: Do you wish she was here instead of me?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">She asks me if I want to see her naked. I guess in some ill-lit cave at the base of my brain stem, I do, but the human in me is tired and just wants to sleep. But I give a little smile and say Yes, because she is fragile in her offering, because she is timid and the forthrightness is difficult for her. If I told her No it would devastate her. She says Okay. She starts to fumble with the top button of her shirt – she is stiff with nerves, performing this part of a girl who knows what to do here. I laugh and put a hand on her hip and pull her toward where I am seated on the edge of the bed. I say Let me. She looks down at me and her hair falls into my eyes. She laughs now and arranges her hair over her shoulder. I reach for her top button and ask Can I? And she nods. I unbutton her shirt and she shrugs it off and looks at me as if for approval. I slide my hands over her thin shoulders and down to her waist and pretend to be more overcome with desire than I am. Normally I would not have to pretend, but at the moment I want to sleep. I put my head against her stomach and close my eyes. She runs her fingers through my hair and this does give me a rush of pleasure – I have always liked the feeling of someone’s nails tracing over my scalp. It gives me chills. I hook my fingers on the inside of her waistband and make my way around to the front and ask Can I, and she says Yes, and I unbutton her jeans and take them down without opening my eyes. I really am tired. I pull her down and onto my lap and hold onto her, and she holds my head but there is the lingering question of What now? I don’t know how to tell her I just want to sleep. After a minute she says We can just sleep, and I feel myself flush with gratitude. I laugh.</summary></entry></feed>